jacksonville,florida
(杰克逊维 弗罗里达)
you want grapefruit or cranberry?
你想要葡萄柚汁还是越橘汁?
Coffee.
咖啡
Cranberry it is.
那就越橘汁了
Take it easy on the butter.
少吃点黄油
Is half a stick too much?
半勺也多吗?
Yeah,well,I'm just following doctor's orders.
哦 我只是遵循医生嘱咐
It--it would be nice if you did the same.
如--如果你也这么做就好了
Hey,look.
嘿 听着
Laura sent the pictures from her orlando trip.
Laura 给我们寄来了她在 奥兰多旅行时的照片
I wonder if there are any of that new guy that she's so crazy about.
我真想知道有没有让她着迷的男生
Oh,wait a minute.
哦 等一等
I thought she said...
我原以为她说的是...
I thought she said pictures,not a video.
我原以为她说的是照片 不是录像带
That's a dvd,mary.
那是dvd, Mary
Technology isn't slowing down.
科学技术的发展还是那么快
It's actually passing you by.
一切就在你身边发生
If you don't catch up soon,you'll be as pitiful as your mother.
如果你不迎头赶上 你就会像你妈妈一样可惜
Well,that's motivation.
哦 这就是动力
Come on,mary.I could show you a few things.
来吧 Mary 我来给你看点东西
You afraid to be my student?
你怕不怕做我的学生?
"Hi,guys.
"嗨 伙计们
Just wanted to let you know I'm having a great time.Miss you both.
只想让你们知道 我玩得很开心 我很想念你们两个
" Sweet.
甜心
Aw,but sooner or later...
* Aw, but sooner or later... *
wait a minute.This...
慢着 这...
is that laura?
那是Laura 吗?
The one it can't be.
那不可能是
frank,what's happening?
Frank 怎么了?
oh,my god.
哦 上帝啊
this was sent to the family?
这个被寄给了她的家人?
Father had a heart condition,died while watching it.
父亲有心脏病 观看的时候病发死亡了
so the music's not added like a regular soundtrack.
这么说音乐不是像普通配乐 那样添加上去的
It's in the background,so if you turn it down,you also turn down the voices.
是背景音乐 所以如果你调轻音乐 人声也轻了
Well,can't we get garcia to separate the audio tracks?
我们就不能让Garcia 分离声道吗?
She's working on it noW.
她已经在做了
Well,the sooner we hear how he talks to the victim,the sooner we'll know what kind of man we're dealing with.
越早了他跟受害人讲话的方式 我们就能越快知道要对付的是哪种人
Tell us about laura clemensen.
说说Laura clemensen 的情况
20 years old.
20 岁
Sophomore at jacksonville university in florida.
弗罗里达杰克逊维大学的大二学生
Assumed to be the fifth in a series of rapes and murders over the past 2 years.
可能是近两年里的第五例连环奸杀案
Some women were abducted in parking lots,others while they were running.
一些女性是在停车场遭绑架的 一些则是在跑步时遭遇不幸的
And when was she reported missing?
她什么时候被报告失踪?
Technically she wasn'T.
程序上讲, 并没有
Roommate thought she was visiting family.
室友以为她去看望父母
Family thought she was at school.
父母以为她在学校
Close to her family?
和家人联系紧密吗?
Very.She had dinner with them on sunday.
非常紧密 周日还一起共进了晚餐
That was 5 days ago,and nobody's seen her until now.
那是五天之前 从此就没人见过她了
She wasn't killed on the tape.
带子里她没有被杀
And given forensics,other victims were tortured for weeks before they were killed,so
鉴于法医学证据 其他的受害者 在被杀前都被折磨了几星期
I think we should operate as if she's still alive.
所以, 我认为我们应该 按照她还活着的思想办案
Not for long,if the bastard gets his way.
不会太久 如果那混蛋照安排行事
Ok,I don't get it.
好吧 我不明白
This is the fifth abduction and now the second dvd.
这是第五起绑架案 第二盘dvd
Why'd they wait to call this in?
他们怎么到现在才提交上来?
The last victim's family received this dvd 2 months ago.
最后一个受害者家庭在 两个月前收到这盘dvd
Jacksonville P.D.Thought maybe they'd get some more clues instead of just raise more questions.
杰克逊维警察觉得他们可以从中找到 更多线索而不是提出更多疑问
Can you turn that down,please?
把声音调低点  行吗?
There seems to be a natural escalation to the murders.
这里有个很自然升级到谋杀的过程
It began as brutal attacks against the victims,and now it's psychological attacks to the families.
一开始是对受害者残忍的攻击 接着是对她家人心灵的摧残
So if the thrill of the kill isn't enough to satisfy his sadistic needs,he needs to spread panic,and he thrives on that.
所以对杀戮的激动不足以 满足他施虐需要 他就需要扩大恐慌
Sadistic killers are typically strangers to their victims.
施虐性杀手是受害者不认识的人
It's--it's easier for the offender to torture and kill someone that they don't know.
这样--这样罪犯会容易对他们不认识 的人进行折磨和残杀
Offenders.
罪犯们
Man on the tape isn't doing this just for himself.
带子上的那个人 并不是为自己才这么做的
He's playing to an audience,not her family.
他在为观众表演 不是她的家人
Someone watching...
在观看的某人...
who can appreciate what he's doing,admire his sadistic skills.
能够欣赏他在做的事情 钦佩他施虐的技巧
It is a characteristic of partners to record their crimes so they can relive the fantasy later.
应该有个特定的搭档在拍摄犯罪过程 这样稍候他们就能再次体验"胜境"
How can we be sure?
我们怎么肯定呢?
Right there.The camera moves.
就在这 摄像机移动了
one guy tortures while the other records it.
一个人施虐 另一个拍摄
Master and servant.
主人和仆人
Jacksonville P.D.'S been looking for this killer for years.
杰克逊维的警察们 这几年一直在找这个杀手
How long is it gonna take 'em to find a team?
看看他们找到这么一个组合要多久?
Mark twain once wrote,"of all the animals,"man is the only one that is cruel.
马克吐温曾经写道 "在所有的动物中, 人类是唯一残忍的"
"He is the only one that inflicts pain for the pleasure of doing it.
"他是唯一因为快感而施虐的动物"
" Again.
又来了
That's the third time he's looked back at the camera.
这是第三次他回头看摄像机
He's looking back at his partner.
他在回头看他的搭档
Hotch: These two are clearly deranged and acting out their worst sadistic fantasies.
他们两个很明显异常兴奋 演出他们施虐的狂想
Foile ?deux.
共有型妄念
Rare psychological phenomenon in which 2 or more people share the same psychotic delusion.
一种2 个或以上的人患有同一种 妄想的罕见精神现象
In its literal translation,yes,but it often refers to the bond that exists between 2 people that bring out the worst in each other.
从字面的翻译 是的 但通常指的是 让两个人暴露出最可怕一面的一种纽带
Most killing teams have a dominant personality that instigates and plans and a submissive one who's the eager accomplice.
大多数谋杀团队都有一个占支配地位的人 煽动计划, 还有一个屈从的人作为帮凶
So how do they decide who gets to kill?
那么他们怎么决定谁来动手?
Well,the dominant one will usually insist on taking the life.
通常由占支配地位的人动手
So what's the psychology behind making these dvds?
那么在拍摄这些dvd 的背后 有着怎样的心理?
It's a shared souvenir,allows the dominant to keep the submissive one motivated,loyal,and aroused.
这是一个分享的纪念品 可以使支配者 给予服从者积极性 忠诚和激励
It's also about control.
还有控制
Built-in insurance policy for blackmail,just in case somebody gets cold feet.
是拿来勒索的保障 以防万一有人胆小退缩
It makes you wonder what might have happened if these 2 people never had met.
你不禁会想如果这俩个人 从未谋面会怎样
Chances are the women would still be alive.
要是这些女人还活着就有机会知道
Jacksonville P.D.Just located laura clemensen's body.
杰克逊维警察刚刚找到了 Laura clemensen 的尸体
Some hikers found her under a bridge.
登山者在一座桥下发现了她的尸体
They never hide them.They're always easy to find.
他们从未藏匿过尸体 它们总是很容易就被发现
Guys,laura clemensen wasn't missing for more than a week.
伙计们 Laura clemensen 失踪还不到一星期
The time spent torturing's getting shorter.
用来折磨的时间减短了
Has her mother been notified?
通知她母亲了吗?
No.Not yet.
不 还没有
We can cover more ground if we split up.
如果我们分来行动 可能收获更广
Morgan and I'll meet local P.D.At the scene.
Morgan 和我去现场见见当地警察
I'll talk to laura clemensen's mother,and since she just lost her husband...
我去和Laura clemensen 母亲谈谈 考虑到她刚刚失去丈夫...
I'll go with you.
我跟你一起去
I'll start with the victimology,maybe find the reason why these women were targeted.
我从受害者心理学着手 可能会找到为什么她们会被盯上
Mary: After frank and i watched that video,I-- I knew.
Frank 和我看过那盘带子后 我-- 我就知道
At least she isn't suffering anymore.
至少她不再受苦了
Is there anything that we can do for you?
有什么我们可以帮忙的吗?
Um,F...
嗯...
frank gave laura a-- a pearl and diamond ring for graduation.
Frank 送给Laura 一个-- 珍珠钻石戒指作为毕业礼物
Could I get it back?
我能拿回来吗?
I will look into that right away.
我会留心找到的
Thank you.
谢谢
As part of our investigation,we're trying to gain some insight into your daughter,
作为我们调查的一部分 我们要试着进一步了解您的女儿
and,uh,I wondered whether she was...
我想知道她是...
shy and quiet,or was she more outgoing and made friends easily?
害羞安静还是比较外向 容易交友?
I mean,is this really important?
这真的很重要吗?
Yes,ma'am.I know that this is hard,but
是的 女士 我知道这有些困难 但是
the more similarities we can find between the victims,the more it'll help us narrow down who's responsible.
我们能找出越多受害者共同点 越能帮助我们缩小寻找范围
frank had a ball in her hand from the minute she could walk.
Frank 从她学会走路起 就对她宠爱有加
She was confident.
她很自信
She knew everybody at school.
她认识学校里的每一个人
She thought of our oldest,patrick,as her best friend.
她关心老人 把Patrick作为她最好的朋友
You know,she was like most girls her age.
你知道 她和同龄人一样
She wanted everybody to like her.
她希望人人都喜欢她
Frank used to think that she was too much of a people pleaser,
Frank 曾觉得她太受人们欢迎了
but I think it shows a really good heart.
但我觉得这正体现了她的善良
I do,too.
我也是
The police told us that they may have a-- they may have a witness who saw laura giving someone directions.
警方告诉我们他们可能有一个 -- 目击者看见Laura 给人指路
Does that sound like something she would have done?
这听上去像不像她会做的事?
We--we raised our children to be...
我们--我们教育我们的孩子...
helpful and--and kind,and--and that made laura an easy target for a killer?
要做乐于助人--和善的人-- 这却让Laura成为容易受攻击的对象?
You have to know that you and frank did everything right.
你必须知道你和Frank 作的对
Frank was supposed to be at work yesterday,and if laura-- if laura hadn't driven back to-- to campus that night,I mean,
我是说Frank昨天本该上班 如果laura -- 如果Laura昨晚没有开车回-- 学校
this-- this wasn't supposed to happen.
这-- 这本不应该发生
This wasn't s--
这不应该--
Special agents gideon and morgan.
Gideon 和Morgan 特工
Detective robert portillo.
Robert Portillo 探员
This is the fifth girl on my watch in the past 2 years,and we still don't have a viable suspect.
这是我调查的两年间第五个女孩了 而我们还没有可以追踪的嫌疑犯
We think you're looking for 2 men.
我们认为你在找的是两个人
Really?Based upon what evidence?
真的? 基于什么证据?
Well,given the level of sadistic torture and desire to document their crimes,
基于施虐的程度 和记录犯罪的欲望
we're confident this was done by a killing team.
我们很肯定这是出于杀人组合作为
She's got deep lacerations on her neck,chest,and thighs.
在颈部胸部和大腿上有很深的撕裂伤
From the color of the bruising,torture went on for several days.
从擦伤的颜色来看 折磨持续了有好几天
Csi believes the cause of death was ligature strangulation,and it is consistent with the other victims.
罪案现场调查科认为死因是绳索勒死 这和其他受害者一样
In the video,she's wearing a pearl ring on her left hand.
录像中 她左手戴着一枚珍珠戒指
No other evidence has turned up.
没有其他证据
They've combed the area,quarter-mile radius.
他们以四分之一英里为半径 地毯式搜寻了整个区域
Why would they need more trophies,gideon?
为什么他们还需要战利品Gideon?
Maybe passed it along as a gift.
也许作为礼物送出去
Like the green river killer?
就像绿河杀手?
Yeah.
是的
He'd leave jewelry for his female coworkers and then become aroused when he saw them wear it.
他为他的女性同事留下了珠宝 然后当他看见她们佩戴感觉兴奋
After everything they do to these girls,why do they leave 'em in these horrible positions?
他们这么对待这些姑娘之后 为什么要把她们放置成这种姿势?
Haven't they suffered enough?
她们受苦受得还不够吗?
Apparently not.
显然不够
This is the ultimate degradation to the victim and her family.
这是对受害者及其家属的终极侮辱
Shock value for whoever finds them.
让找到她们的人震惊的资本
And it sends a message to the police.
同时也给警方传达了一条讯息
What's that?
什么?
"Look what we can do.
看看我们能做的
You can't stop us.
你们阻止不了我们
" Are there new victims?
有新的受害者吗?
Garcia just sent a list over of all the unsolved rapes and murders in the past 3 years.
Garcia 刚刚把过去三年未结案奸杀案 列了一份清单
There are 2 that are particularly interesting.
有两起尤其有趣
They look the type.
她们看起来象是同一种类型
Anything else?
还有吗?
Well,aside from sharing similar physical traits,they were also posed.
除了有相同的体征 她们都被摆了姿势
The only difference is they were manually strangled,which I think is why jacksonville P.D.Didn't find a connection.
唯一的不同就是她们是被用手扼死的 我认为这正是警方没找到联系的原因
We find dna on the first 2?
我们在最初两起案子里找到了DNA?
That's the thing.
就是这个
It didn't match the recent kills,but check this out.
和最近的凶案不符 但看看这个
What if the dominant one allowed the submissive one to rape the first 2 victims in order to sort of draw him in,
要是支配者允许服从者 强奸最初的两个 好把他吸引进来
and then once he's hooked,he began keeping the prize all for himself?
然后一旦他上钩 他开始自己干?
You tell morgan and gideon about this yet?
你告诉Morgan 和Gideon 这个了吗?
They're still at the crime scene.
他们还在犯罪现场
We confirmed that laura clemensen had good relationships with her family and friends.
我们证实了Laura Clemensen 和家人朋友关系很好
She got good grades and stayed out of trouble.
她成绩很好 也不惹麻烦
Just like all the other victims.
跟其他受害者一样
Did you guys notice that the package sent to the clemensen family was only sent to mary?
你们注意到没有给Clemensen 家的 包裹就寄给了Mary 一个人?
What about the first dvd?
第一盘dvd 呢?
Um,let me...
嗯 让我...
Why are they targeting the mothers?
他们为什么就给母亲看?
The mother asked god to forgive the people responsible.
母亲请求上帝宽恕有罪的人
Hotch: And?
还有呢?
The family that received the first dvd went on tv pleading for their daughter's life.
收到第一盘dvd 的家人 上电视祈求饶他们女儿一命
That must have made the unsubs angry.
这一定让不明人物很生气
So sending the dvd to the mother is a message in itself.
所以给母亲寄dvd 本身就有寓意
A very clear one.
非常清晰
They don't want or need forgiveness.
他们不想要或者不需要宽恕
How do you get to the freeway?
请问怎么上高速?
If you back out to warner and make a right,you'll see the exit in about half a mile.
如果你回到Warner 街 再右转你就会在半英里外看到入口
Thanks.
谢谢
No problem.
不用谢
We're up to 7 victims now?
我们现在有7 个受害者了?
jacksonville police dept
(杰克逊维警察局)
The humiliating posing of the body can't be a coincidence.
把尸体摆成这种虐待姿势不会是巧合
It's just too unique.
太特别了
The bruising on the necks.
颈部的瘀痕
Looks to me like the first victim struggled.
似乎第一个受害者挣扎过
I'd say the killer probably lost his grip a couple times and really had to fight these women.
凶手可能有时不能掌控 又一定要和这些女人搏斗
That's why he switched from bare hands to a ligature.
所以他从赤手空拳 转变成了用绳索捆绑
It's more efficient,controlled,and it doesn't sacrifice his sadistic need for a slow death.
这样更有效 更有控制力 也不会牺牲他对慢性死亡的残酷需求
Because the dna didn't match,jacksonville P.D.Just didn't put it together.
因为DNA不吻合 杰克逊维警方才没能联系起来
Yeah,and since the weren't looking for 2 offenders...
是啊 既然他们不是寻找两个凶手...
signature indicates these women had the same killers.
签名的字迹显示 这些女人被相同凶手所害
We just need to figure out who the hell they are.
我们只需查处他们究竟是谁
Well,jacksonville P.D.Searched everywhere,even swamps,and still didn't find the victims' vehicles.
杰克逊维警方搜寻了各处 甚至沼泽 还是没找到受害者的车
I got garcia tracing vins,but my guess is they dispose of the cars just like they do the women.
我让Garcia追踪车牌号码 但我猜他们同样也处理了车子
Yeah,but the bodies are easy to find.
但是尸体很容易被发现
Why do they go to so much trouble to hide the cars?
他们又何必多费事去藏车呢?
I didn't think it could get any hotter than yesterday.
昨天已经再热不过了
Today's a record breaker,and the A.C.'S busted.Sorry about the fans.
今天可是打破纪录了 空调也罢工 风扇也没用
They're probably spreading more dust than cool air.
只能散播灰尘而不是冷空气
Well,we won't keep your officers too long.
我们不会让你们的警官待太久
That's not to say that the submissive partner is in any way pure or innocent in this exchange.
并不是说服从者在这场交易中 是纯洁或无辜的
If their criminal desire wasn't present,their partnership wouldn't work.
如果没有犯罪的欲望 这种搭档形式也不可能奏效
The offenders share a common delusion.
凶手有着共同的妄想症
It's one that you and i would never accept,but it's this bond that justifies their actions.
是这里各位都不会接受的 但正是这种联系解释了他们的行为
So we're looking for 2 sick minds who complete each other.
所以我们在寻找两个有着病态思维 并互相补足对方的人
It's kind of like the perfect storm.
有点像是完美风暴
Once these deviant personalities collide,they're deadly and unstoppable.
一旦这些变态人格相撞 便是致命且难以阻止的
Like the D.C.Snipers or the columbine assassins.
就像华盛顿特区狙击手 或者Columbine高中的暗杀者一样
Sometimes they've met in childhood.
有时他们是从小就认识
Other times,they can be related,like the hillside stranglers,angelo buono and kenneth bianchi,
有时他们有点联系 就像山腰扼杀者 Angelo Buono和Kenneth Bianchi
psychopathic cousins who terrorized women in los angeles.
在洛杉矶恐吓女性的精神病兄弟
The dominant partner makes the submissive one feel invincible.
主导者让服从者感觉无往不胜
That's his reward for doing as he's told.
这就是他听从命令的回报
Unfortunately there are countless opportunities for these twisted minds to meet,
不幸的是 有无以数计的机会 让这些扭曲的思想相遇
and once they've pulled off their vicious acts,
一旦他们实施残忍的行为
the two accept this as common behavior and become bored with normal activity.
就会当那是日常行为 并且对正常活动感到厌倦
They live only for their new reality.
他们只为自己的新现实而活
They're obsessed with it,addicted to it.
沉溺于之 成瘾于之
And there's a fierce loyalty between the two.
他们之间也有暴力性的忠诚
The submissive one,however,is usually less intelligent and easier to catch,and once caught,he is easier to turn.
服从者 通常没那么聪明 容易被抓 也容易招供
Lack of remorse increas their aggressiveness.
缺少痛悔感 增加了他们的进攻意识
Sexual sadists will stop when they're caught.
性虐待狂要被抓时才会停止作案
And the need to psychologically torture the families-- sorry to interrupt.
- 而精神上折磨家人的这种需求-- - 对不起打断一下
If you've seen my daughter,please,tiffany's all I have.
如果你看见我的女儿 拜托 Tiffany是我的唯一
She--she went for a run last night,and she never came home.
她昨晚出去跑步 就再也没回家
She's my baby.
她是我的心肝宝贝
Why weren't we told about this before she went on the news?
为什么她上新闻之前 没人通知我们?
'Cause we didn't know about it.
因为我们不知情
Tiffany was abducted from middleberg.
Tiffany是在Middleberg被绑架
That's nearly an hour away,and it's outside of jacksonville's jurisdiction.
要一个小时的车程 并且超出杰克逊维的管辖区域
Are you sure these are the same offenders?
你确定这些是相同的凶手吗?
Well,she's their type.
她是他们要的类型
Grabbed her while jogging,just like their third victim.
在她慢跑时抓走她 就像第三个受害者一样
Middleberg's only an hour from here?
Middleberg离这里就一小时吗?
If they see this,it's just a matter of time before they send a dvd.
如果他们看见这个 那送DVD过来只是时间问题
All right,jennifer jareau,fbi.
好的 Jennifer Jareau FBI
You just aired a press conference with beverly spears.
你刚和Beverly Spears发表了新闻发布会
I need to speak to her immediately.
我要马上跟她说话
These guys are impatient.
这些人真没耐心
They just dumped laura clemensen's body 24 hours ago.
24小时前他们刚刚 丢弃Laura Clemensen的尸体
Which means they're more dangerous than they were yesterday,and tiffany spears is running out of time.
也就是说他们比昨天更危险 Tiffany Spears时间不多了
You ok?
你好了吗？
Am I ok?
我好了吗？
Uh,let me see.
恩 让我想想
I've got images of a girl being tortured burned inside my brain over the strains of this once-carefree choice of music.
我脑子里全是女孩被折磨的画面 还伴着惬意的音乐
I've isolated 4 sources from one track,and each one is more distorted than the next,
我从一个声道分割出四个来源 每一个都比下一个更失真
so no,I am not ok,and it's gonna take awhile.
所以 我还没好 还需要点时间
Penelope,you know I appreciate you doing this.
Penelope 你知道我很感激你这么做
Thank you,sugar.
谢谢你 甜心
For right now,even that doesn't feel good.
但现在 即使那样也感觉不好
Eh,moving on.
继续工作
Some of these victims were abducted while driving.
有些受害者是在开车时被绑架
It does leave a nice trail,especially when all the parts lead you to trevor's used auto in georgia.
确实留下了很好的线索 尤其当零部件 指向乔治亚的Trevor二手车库
Well,no wonder jacksonville P.D.Couldn't find the vehicles.
难怪杰克逊维的警察找不到车子
The unsubs didn't drive the cars.
这些不明人士根本没有开车
They destroyed them and sold the parts.
他们毁了它们 并卖了零部件
Yeah,and over state lines.
没错 跨过州际线
These sickos are good.
这些神经病太狡猾了
Parts were found in georgia.
在乔治亚州找到了零部件
Sales were traced to a joey davin,who lives right here in jacksonville.Joseph P.
根据买卖记录 追踪到一个人 叫Joey Davin 就住在杰克逊维
Davin,27.
Joseph P. Davin 27岁
In and out of jail since he was 17.
自17岁起就是监狱的常客
Number of charges,including car theft with a partner.
许多控罪 包括和别人搭档偷车
Maybe he likes to team up.
也许他喜欢组队行动
Either way,he hasn't learned his lesson.
不管怎样 他都没有接受教训
Doesn't sound too smart to me.
似乎不太聪明啊
Exactly why he needs a good leader.
所以他才要一个好的领导者
If it is proof that tiffany is still alive,still breathing,I need to see it.
如果有证据显示Tiffany还活着 还呼吸着 我就要去看看
Ma'am,you don't understand.
女士 你不明白
Do you remember what tiffany was wearing the last time you saw her?
你还记得最后一次见Tiffany时 她穿什么衣服吗?
I told the police she was going for a run.
我跟警方说过 她出去跑步
Sneakers,tank,shorts.
运动鞋 背心 短裤
Well,you need to think of her like this until we get her back.
在我们找回她之前 你就想着这样的她
You don't need to see what's on that dvd.
你不需要看DVD里面的东西
I was supposed to have run with her yesterday.
昨天我应该陪她去跑步的
I should have been there.
我应该在那的
Help her,please,god.
救救她 上帝啊
Help her.
救救她
Investigators are connecting tiffany spears' disappearance with those of the 5 other victims murdered in the jacksonville area,
调查人员将Tiffany Spears的失踪案 和杰克逊维的另五起谋杀案联系在一起
including laura clemensen,whose body was found yesterday.
其中包括昨天发现的尸体 Laura Clemensen
3 of the victims' cars are still missing.
其中三名受害者的车还未找到
Investigators believe if they can find who took those cars,they will find the killer responsible.
调查人员相信 只要发现谁拿了车 就能找出真正的凶手
Fbi.
FBI
And what can I do for you?
有什么能帮忙吗?
We're looking for joseph davin.
我们找Joseph Davin
What did joey do now?
Joey又做了什么?
Sir,we really need to talk to joey.
先生 我们真的需要和Joey谈谈
You joseph davin?
你是Joseph Davin?
Get out of my way.
别挡道
Joey,don't be stupid!
Joey 别犯傻
I saw it on tv.3 strikes,and I'm out.
我看了电视 我被三振出局了
I'm not goin' back.
我不会回去的
I'm n--I'm not goin' down for this.
我不...我不会为此倒下的
Put the weapon down.
放下武器
Put it down now!
放下武器! 现在!
Joey,put--
Joey! 放下--
Oh,joey!
噢 Joey!
Why didn't he put down the gun?
他为什么不肯放下武器呢?
He didn't want that third strike.
他不想被第三振
I didn't have a choice.
我没得选择
And he was our closest link to finding tiffany spears.
他是我们找到Tiffany Spears的 最接近线索
Can't this wait?
不能再等等吗?
Mr.Davin,there have been 7 women raped and murdered in the jacksonville area.
Davin先生 在杰克逊维地区 已经有七名女性被奸杀
We can tie joe to 3 of them.
我们相信Joey和其中三名有关
You know,I thought by forcing him to move back in here,it would keep him out of trouble.
你知道 我以为把他藏在这里 就能让他没事
How long had your son been living here?
你儿子住在这里多久?
2 years.
两年
After the M.S.Put me in the chair.
自从多样硬化症让我坐上这椅子之后
Was he still running with his boys from prison?
他还和他的狱友一起混吗?
Aw,he works at a garage with a bunch of ex-cons.
他和一群前科犯在汽车修理厂工作
I tried so hard.
我已经尽力了
I just couldn't get him out of that world.
就是没法把他带出那个圈子
I kept telling him,"you're better than all this.
我一直跟他说"你应该更好些"
" Agent gideon,we just found this.
Gideon探员 我们刚刚发现这个
Your son have a friend or girlfriend with long,blond hair?
你儿子有没有什么朋友或女朋友 是长长的金黄色头发的?
Not that I know of,no.
据我所知没有
Is it possible that you wouldn't know if you did?
有没有可能是你不知道他有?
After today...
今天之后...
nothing would surprise me.
没有什么事能让我惊讶
Morgan: The dominant one wouldn't have panicked like that.
主导者不会那样惊慌的
He would have come at us shooting and gone down in a blaze of glory.
他会冲着我们开枪 并在光辉荣耀中倒下
So where's the other half of this partnership?
那么另一人在哪里呢?
Witnesses saw a white minivan,correct?
有证人看见一辆白色MINIVAN 是吗? (克莱斯勒汽车)
Morgan: That one's henry'S.
那个是Henry的
It's got handicapped plates.
有残疾人车牌
You see any signs in henry's behavior that he could be part of this?
你觉得从Henry的行为看 他有可能是俩搭档之一吗?
Nah.
没有
But if joey drives the van,then he can drive while his partner snatches the girls.
但如果是Joe开的车 他搭档就可以抓走女孩
Have your men process the van.
你们检查过那辆车吗?
If there's anything in there that doesn't belong to joe or henry davin,I wanna know about it.
如果有任何不属于Joe 或Henry Davin的东西 我都要知道
So,how does joe meet his partner?
那么Joe是怎么和他搭档见面的呢?
Well,his father says he hangs with a bunch of ex-cons at the garage.
他父亲说他一直和汽车修理厂的 一群前科犯混在一起
Yeah.It's,uh-- it's in springfield.
恩 那在Springfield
I'll have hotch check it out.
我已经让Hotch去那看看了
If he's still hanging with ex-cons,he probably talks to his old cellmate.
如果他还和前科犯们在一起 那就可能和他监狱室友联系
Find out who that is.
查查那人是谁
Ok.
好的
This better be hella good.
最好说句好听的
Garcia?
Garcia?
Hello.
喂
Yes,sir.
是的 长官
I'm here.I'm sorry.
我在这里 对不起
I just--I wasn't--I'm surprised that you're calling me.
我只是...我不... 我没想到你会... 打来
I need to know who joseph davin shared a cell with.
我想知道Joseph Davin以前 和谁住一间牢房?
Yes.Sure.
好的
Uh,it was a guy...
是一个小伙子...
named...
名叫...
His name was tony canardo.
他的名字叫Tony Canardo
They were in together for 18 months,and both were released 3 years ago.
他们在一起住了18个月 三年前都被释放
Before the killings started.
就在屠杀开始之前
Is that it?
是吗?
His current address is 865 kentwood in jacksonville.
他目前住址是杰克逊维市Kentwood街865号
That's all you got?
你就查到这么多?
Uh,yeah.
是的
Garcia...
Garcia...
yes.
是
You do great work.
你做的很不错
Keep it up.
继续努力
Oh,thank you,sir.
噢 谢谢长官
Thank you.
谢谢你
Man: Look,I got 2 guys out today.
听着 今天两个员工不在
I can't help you.
我没法帮你
But my car's still leaking oil.
但我的车还在漏油
Do you still have a receipt?
你收据还在吗?
It was less than a month ago.
还不到一个月阿
Hotch: Excuse me.
不好意思
I'm with a customer.
我这里还有顾客
All right.
好吧
What can you tell me about joe davin?
你对Joe Davin了解多少?
I can tell you i fired him last week.
上周我炒了他
Why?
为什么?
He wasn't very good at his job.
他干活不怎么好
He was shot this morning by jacksonville police.
他今早被杰克逊维警方击毙了
Sorry to hear that.
真是抱歉
You seem real upset by the news.
听到这消息 你似乎很"不安"
I already had another guy to take his place.
我已经找了代替他的人
Well,you didn't waste any time,did you?
你没有浪费时间 是吗?
His ex-con buddies were always at the shop.
他的那些前科犯兄弟总在这里游荡
It's bad for business.
对我的生意不好
You're an ex-con.
你也是前科犯
I was innocent.
我是无辜的
Yeah.They all are.
是阿 每个人都这么说
You know this guy?
你认识这个人吗?
That's t-bone.
那是T-bone
Name's tony canardo.
他叫Tony Canardo
He ran with joey's crowd.
他和Joey那群人一起混的
This is one of the ex-cons that you were talking about?
是不是你刚刚说的那些前科犯之一?
Yeah.
没错
When tony's around,joey's not taking orders from me,and I can't have too many cooks in the kitchen.
Tony在的时候 Joey从不听我命令 "一山不容二虎"
You know what I mean?
你知道我的意思吧?
We do.
我们明白
Look,I gotta get back to work.
我要回去工作了
Well,joey was just surrounded by dominant personalities.
Joey被主导性的人格紧紧包围着
If mike kroger was the killer,you'd think he'd try to hide it better.
如果Mike Kroger是凶手 他最好掩饰得好一些
We'll have garcia run his sheet.
让Garcia去翻翻他的底
Who are you guys?
你们是谁?
MrS.Canardo.
Canardo太太
Can we come in?
能进来吗?
Everything ok?
一切都还好吧?
Uh,you tell me.
你说呢
We're looking for your husband.
我们找你丈夫
He's not home.
他不在家
Well,he spent time in prison with a man named joseph davin.
他在狱中和 一个叫Joseph Davin的人在一起
Do you know him?
你认识他吗?
Yeah,I know joey.
是的 我认识Joey
Joey's dead.
Joey死了
Oh,my god.What happened?
我的天 怎么会的?
He pulled a gun when we were trying to question him.
我们要审问他时 他掏出手枪要反击
About what?
审问他什么?
7 young women in the jacksonville area who've been raped and killed.
杰克逊维市的七名女性奸杀案
Did you know him well?
你很了解他吗?
He and my husband did time together.
他和我丈夫确实曾在一起
When tony got out on good behavior,he tried to turn his life around,stay clean.
当Tony因表现好而出狱后 他想要重新来过 远离污秽
How's he doing?
他进展得怎样?
Ok.
还不错
Some of those are mine.
有一些是我的
Tony ever get into trouble or do anything that scares you when he drinks?
Tony喝酒后惹过什么麻烦 或者做过什么吓着你的事吗?
Only when he's around joey.
只有当他和Joey在一起时
Those two get together,I'm afraid of what could happen.
他们俩在一起的时候 我就担心会有什么发生
Do you know where we can find tony now?
你知道哪里可以找到Tony吗?
He's getting off work.
他要下班了
He should be home soon.
应该很快回家
Is there anyplace you can go?
你可以去其他地方吗?
'Cause we're gonna need to talk to him.
因为我们想和他谈谈
I can call my friend kim.
我可以找我朋友Kim
You wanna drive me down to the station?
你能送我去车站吗?
Can you wait here for tony?
你在这里等Tony吧?
Did you run mike kroger's sheet,the guy from the garage?
你查过Mike Kroger的资料了吗 那个修理厂的人?
The boy needs a refresher course in anger management.
这家伙真需要上控制情绪的补习班
Ok,we got assault and battery.
有过施暴 殴打
We got assault with a deadly weapon.
还用致命武器攻击
There's one attempted rape,but it was dropped,because the poor thing was too scared to testify against mr.Stinky.
还有一起企图强奸 但最终放弃诉讼 因为可怜的女孩太害怕不敢指正"臭先生"
Where was he when tiffany spears was abducted?
Tiffany Spears被绑架时 他在哪里?
His credit card says miami,but not all of his alibis check out,
信用卡记录证实是在迈阿密 但并非所有不在场证据都核实过
and you know if there is one loose thread,I will find it,I will pull it,and his story will completely unravel.
只要还有一丝线索 我就会查到底 到时他的谎话就会拆穿
A tout alors.
拜拜! (法语)
Uh,garcia's checking mike kroger's whereabouts when the women were abducted.
Garcia正在查询那女人被绑架时 Mike Kroger身在何处
Some of his alibis already check out.
有些不在场证明已经核实过了
What about tony canardo?
Tony Canardo那边怎么样?
Morgan's still outside his house waiting.
Morgan还在他家门外等他
Officer: Excuse me.
不好意思
Agent gideon,there's someone here who wants to talk to you.
Gideon探员 有人找你
Mrs.Canardo.
Canardo太太
What happened?
发生什么了?
After you left,I got nervous,so I went to find tony.
你们走之后 我很紧张 就去找Tony
Please,sit down.
请坐
And he--he knew something was up,so...
他...他知道有事发生了 所以...
you got a kleenex?
你有纸巾吗?
What'd you tell him?
你跟他说什么?
Well,I told him the truth,that the fbi was asking questions.
我告诉了他事实 FBI来问话
So he hit you?
然后他打了你?
I wasn't completely honest with you about tony.
我并没有对你们坦白Tony的所有事
He fell off the wagon a while ago.
一阵子前 他从货车上摔下
I just was afraid to say something.
我只是害怕说出来
I didn't wanna betray him.He's my husband.
我不想要背叛他 他是我丈夫
No,it's--it's good that you're here with us.
不 你能站在我们这边很好
You're safe here.
你在这里很安全
I'm gonna go tell portillo and hotch that they should meet morgan.
我去告诉Portillo和Hotch 他们该去Morgan那里
Uh,ms.Canardo,can i ask you a question?
Canardo太太 能问你个问题吗?
Yes.
可以
Uh,is that ring new?
这个戒指是新的吗?
Tony won some money playing poker.
Tony玩扑克赢了些钱
He bought it as a gift.
他买来送给我的
Why?
怎么了?
Looks a lot like laura clemensen'S.
看起来很像Laura Clemensen的
Big mistake.
你犯了大错
Come on!
来吧!
Morgan! Yeah!Right here!
- Morgan! - 这里!
What,you couldn't wait?
你等不及了吗?
I didn't want him to get away.
我不想让他逃走
You all right? Yeah.I'm fine.
- 你还好吧? - 是的
Say anything?
他说什么了吗?
No.
没有
You should have stuck to beating up girls.
你还是乖乖地只和女人斗吧
Bring him inside.
把他带进来
Thank you.
谢谢
The tapes are sitting right out.
有人查过这些吗?
We were never in this room.We never saw them.
我们没来过这房间 从没看过这些
it's tiffany spears.
是Tiffany Spears
where is she?
她在哪里?
Help!
救命!
Help me!
谁来救救我!
Help!
快来呀!
Help.
救命哪!
If we're gonna get anything out of tony,we gotta praise him.
要能从他嘴里打探到消息 就得先取悦他
He's the dominant.He thinks he deserves it.
他是主导者 他觉得这一切都是他应得的
Confirm instead of undermine his expectations.
不要去否定他的想法 给他点希望
Make him think he's smarter than us because he saw it coming.
让他以为自己仍然掌控着全局
We don't have much time.
我们没有多少时间了
I know.I'm sorry.That's just standard procedure.
不好意思 这是我们的正常程序
I'm special agent aaron hotchner.
我是aaron hotchner特工
I'm supervising this task force.
特遣部队的主管
I just wanna say that this case,your case,is,uh...
不如跟我来谈谈你的案子吧 它...
remarkable.
最近闹的人竟皆知
You've got people at the B.A.U.Shaking their heads.
BAU的人对你简直恨之入骨
Tony: What about you?
那你对我有什么看法呢?
You shaking your head?
你也很厌恶我吗?
Absolutely.
当然
7 victims in 3 years.
你在3年内杀死了7个人
You've got every woman in jacksonville living in fear.
让杰克逊维尔的女性居民 成日惶恐不安
That's pretty much what you wanted,isn't it?
这比你想要的好很多是吧?
Well,I'm sure whoever's responsible for it is enjoying it.
那个做这事的人一定很享受这个
The B.A.U.Would like to show your interview,with your permission,of course.
如果你同意的话 B.A.U.希望公开你的审讯
Show me what's in the boxes.
那盒子里装着什么
This.
这个盒子
They're all full.
是你的资料
It's all you.
它可是装的满满的
We can,uh--we can open all the boxes if you want.
如果你想的话 我可以打开所有盒子
No.
不用了
I wanna see my lawyer.
我要见我的律师
Well,tony sure lawyered up quick.
哦 tony这么早求要见律师了
He's playing games.
他在跟我们玩游戏
Deal if you tell us where tiffany spears is.
没问题 只要你告诉我tiffany在哪
This guy's been to jail before.
这家伙有过入狱记录
He knows how to keep his mouth shut.
他知道应该怎么对付我们
What do you think,I'm stupid?
你以为呢 我又不是笨蛋
Far from it.
不是
Morgan: Look at that.
看他
Notice how he's focused on those 2 pictures.
正看着那两张照片呢
We can't forensically tie him to those victims,but we're certain that he posed those bodies after death.
我们是不能证明是他杀的人 但是尸体造型绝对是他干的
Well,that's certainly not working.
那招没有用
I'm not getting anywhere with him.
毫无任何进展
Is the wife still here?
他夫人还在这吗?
We wanna put her in a room with him?
让他们两个单独谈谈?
We need to humanize him.
我们需要他正常一点
I think she could do that.
相信他夫人可以做到这点的
How he abuses her.
他总是虐待她
And she takes it.
但她从没反抗过
She's subservient to him.
她能让他发泄
You think she'd do it?
可她会肯吗?
If we wanna find tiffany spears,she'll have to.
要想找到tiffany spears的话 她就必须肯
It's worth a shot.
值得试试
We'd been together 2 years,and we were gonna start a family.
我们在一起两年了 还准备结婚了
Sorry to interrupt.
不好意思打断下
Few minuteS.Thank you.
就几分钟 谢谢
How you holdin' up?
还挺的住吧?
Ok,I guess.
应该可以的
You called your family?
通知你家人了吗?
Tony's my only family.
tony是我唯一的亲人
Tony won't talk to us.
tony不肯和我们合作
What are you gonna do?
你要做什么呢?
I think if you go in there,he'll talk to you.
我觉得 他应该会和你谈谈的
You want me to go in a room with him?
你想要我和他共处一室?
I can't do that.
不行
There--you gotta find another way.
肯定有别的办法的
He'll kill me.I turned him in.
是我把他供出来的 他会杀了我的
Look what he did to me.
看看他都对我做了些什么
I know.
我了解
I believe...
我相信...
That you're the only person who can get through to tony.
你是唯一一个能让tony开口的人
With joe dead,tony's the only one who knows where tiffany spears is.
joe已经死了 只有tony才知道tiffany spears在哪
And if he tells you,you've saved her life.
如果tony告诉你的话 你就能救她了
Right now,you're her only hope.
现在 你是她唯一的希望了
Honey,I need to know where...
宝贝 我想知道...
where the girl is.
那个女孩在哪
Don't you mean...
你是不是在说...
they need to know?
他们想知道?
Why should i tell them anything?
我为什么要告诉他们?
What have I got to gain?
告诉他们我又能有什么好处?
They're pinning us for 7 murders,amber.
他们要告我们7宗谋杀罪呀 amber
I can't believe you and joey killed them all.
我简直不能相信 你和joey居然把那些女孩都杀了
7!
是7个人
None of this would have happened if joey had stayed away.
如果joey不出现的话 这一切都不会发生
We were on our way to better things.
那我们现在也一定过的很快乐
Joey messed that up for us.
joey把一切都给毁了
I need you to tell me,tony.
tony告诉我吧
Where'd joey take the girl?
到底joey把那个女孩关在哪里?
I can'T.
对不起
I'm begging you to end this.
我求求你停止吧
Tell me now.
告诉我吧
Where's the girl?
那个女孩在哪?
There's this...
在一个...
storage unit.
储藏室里
Joe's dad is the only one who has the key.
joe的爸爸是唯一一个有钥匙的人
I can't believe my husband killed all those women.
我丈夫居然杀了这些人 我不能相信
It took a lot of courage to go in there.
我知道你是很艰难的才迈出这一步的
You did the right thing.
做的很好
Can we get you a glass of water or something?
要不要喝杯水或者别的什么?
Yeah.
谢谢
Water?
水吗?
You stay with her,please?
陪着她 好吗?
Yes,sir.
遵命
Joe's dad?Isn't he in a wheelchair,though?
joe的爸爸? 他不是坐轮椅的吗?
Only for the last 2 years.
只是这两年
Henry davin could have raped and killed the first 2 women 3 years ago,then brought in joe and tony to continue his work.
3年前应该是henry davin奸杀了那两个女子 病了之后 他让joe和tony继续他的恶行
Maybe it's the only satisfaction he can get.
也许这是唯一能让他感到满足的事情
Now they record it,and he lives it though them.
他们把过程拍了下来 而他就整天以此为生
So it was a team of 3.
所以是他们3个人共同犯案的咯
We found laura clemensen's hair at henry's house.It makes sense.
怪不得曾在henry的家里找到 laura clemensen的头发
Let's take a ride.
行动
Tony canardo's one sick bastard.
Tony canardo是个混蛋
I'm not surprised mother abandoned him when he was 4,
4岁时 他妈妈抛弃了他 我一点也不奇怪
and then she got clean and got him back until he was 11,when she got busted for prostitution.
但后来她戒了毒又把tony接了回去 直到她因卖淫被捕 那年tony11岁
No wonder he hates women.
怪不得他那么恨女人
He bounced around social services after that.
在那之后他就一直游转于 各福利机构之间了
I mean,this guy never had any support,no foundation,no security.
他从来都没有得过任何人的资助 没有公积金 也没有保险
How'd he get the confidence to pull off something like that?
那他怎么能主导出这么多事来呢?
Maybe that's why he needed a partner.
所以他需要一个同伙呀
But he's supposed to be the dominant one,the leader.
我们原来以为他是主导者
I mean,given his history...
但是你看看他的资料...
how can he do that?
他怎么会有这个能力?
She's not here.
她不在这
She was never here.
她根本就没有被关到过这
What the hell's going on?
发生什么事了
This looks nothing like the video.
这里根本没有摄录机
Reid: He's really playing a tough guy with that officer,huh?
他还真是难缠呀, 哈?
He played the tough guy with hotch.
他在故意跟Hotch耗呢
It wasn't antagonistic.It was defensive.
不是敌意 他只是在进行防卫
False bravado?
假像?
You think he's wearing a mask?
你认为他是装出来的?
Let me see amber's tape.
让我看下amber的带子
Why isn't she scared?
她为什么一点都不紧张?
She looks scared to me.
她很紧张呀
No.
不是的
Look.
你看她
She initiated eye contact right there.
她从一开始就盯着那边
Yeah?
是吗?
You guys have gotta hear this.
你们得听下这个
Patch it through.
接过来吧
If she were afraid,she'd look anywhere but his face.
如果她有害怕的话 她的眼神会游移不定 不敢看他的脸
She's looking at the victims,and she doesn't really...
她一直在看那些被害者 但却没有...
she doesn't seem that repulsed.
很反感那些照片
She actually looks surprisingly calm.
她显的太平静了
Amber: Now put that little bitch on her side.
把她姿势摆好
You like it,don't you?
你很喜欢这样的对吧
Dirty whore likes it.
你这个贱人很喜欢的吧?
He's studying her.
他在等待她
He's waiting for her lead.
他在等她的指示
Where'd joey take the girl?
joey把那个女孩关到哪里去了?
She just gave him an order.
她在给tony下命令
He's protecting her.
tony在保护她
He's giving her an out.
让她能摆脱嫌疑
Amber: Do it again.
再做一次
Gideon: Where is she?
她在哪?
Where's the girl?!
那个女孩在哪!?
Where is she?!
她在那里?!
Told you to watch her.
叫你看着她的
We analyzed what we recorded of tony and amber.
分析过tony和amber的对话记录后
Turns out she's the dominant one.
发现amber才是那个主导者
Garcia finally isolated the soundtrack on that dvd.
Garcia分离出DVD上的声道了
Turns out it was amber giving the orders.
证实是amber发令的
That means she's the one doing the killing.
也就是说人是她杀的咯
Where is amber now?
amber现在在哪?
She told the cop she was going out for a smoke and walked out the back door.
她告诉我们的人说想出去抽根烟 然后就从后门走出去了
We're running out of time.
我们快没时间了
You've gotta find out where they're holding tiffany.
你必须找出tiffany的被关地点
I'll change the approach.
我会换个方式
Uh,you're gonna wanna look at this.
看下这个
Joey davin's dna didn't match the first 2 victims.
joey davin的DNA不符合在前两个 受害者身上找到的DNA
That means neither could henry'S.
就是说她们跟henry没有任何关系
So who raped the first 2 girls?
那是谁强奸了她们呢?
Lucky man,you know that?
幸运小子 你知道吗?
You have something really special.
你小子还真有点本事
I mean,she had to know what you were doing to all those women and stayed with you anyway.
让amber知道了你干了这么多坏事 却还能和你在一起
Must feel great to be appreciated by the woman you love.
被你所爱的人所欣赏 你一定感觉很好
It does. I bet.
- 确实 - 我知道
I know you and amber would do anything for each other.
我知道你和amber 能为对方做任何的事情
But why would you confess to killing these 2 women when you had no idea who they are?
可是你为什么要承认你杀了这两个人呢? 你根本不知道她们是谁
Joey and i killed all of 'em.
joey和我杀了所有的人
Really?
真的呀?
Well,whose dna did we find at the scene?
看看我们在现场找到了谁DNA?
What are you talking about?
你在说什么呢?
Well,it's not yours.It's not joe'S.
不是你的 也不是joe的
That poor guy probably had no idea these cars belonged to the women you killed.
那个可怜的人怀疑根本不知道 那些车是属于被害者的
Makes you wonder if you and joe hadn't shared a cell together,maybe he'd still be alive.
想想吧  如果那时joe不是 和你被关一起的话 也许他就不会死了
You got the wrong idea.
你错了
No,I think you've got the wrong idea,tony.
是你想错了tony
Joe wasn't your partner.
joe不是你的同伙
Tiffany spears isn't at the storage unit.
Tiffany spears也不在那个储藏室里
You wanna know what else?
还想知道些别的什么吗?
We can hear amber's voice on the videos telling you what to do.
经过技术分析 我们在DVD上听见 amber正在指导你如何去做
We know amber's your partner.
我们知道amber才是你的同伙
Come on.
得了吧
Why?
为什么?
Why you protecting her?
为什么那么保护她?
She's  wife.
她是我老婆
It's more than that.
不仅如此吧
Look,nothing would ever come between us-- not you...
没有什么可以破坏我们的关系 你不行...
not nothing.
任何事物都不行
Besides amber would never do anything to hurt me.
还有 amber是不会伤害我的
Reid here.
我是reid
No time for pleasantries.
我不是在和你开玩笑
I was able to unseal a file regarding amber canardo.
我找到了一个 关于amber canardo的评估报告
What does it say?
怎么说的?
When amber was 15,she walked into a tallahassee hospital raped and beaten something awful.
amber15岁时曾在塔拉哈西市立医院 有过严重的强奸与殴打他人行为
Doctors deduced she was being abused by her father and her brother.
医生猜测她曾被父亲和哥哥虐待过
Eventually they convinced her to go to the police.
医生最后说服她去自首
But when she did,mom showed up and told them that amber was lying.
但就在她去的时候 她的母亲出现 并告诉警察amber是在撒谎
She obviously did nothing to protect amber from the abuse.
很明显 她根本没有保护过amber
She--she feels betrayed by her mother and now receives extreme sadistic pleasure in watching the same thing that happened to her.
她觉得母亲背叛了她 再加上现在看见 与她一样的受虐者而产生的变态般的快感
Strange.In this case the abused actually became the abuser.
太奇特了 受虐者摇身一变成为施虐者了
That doesn't happen a lot?
不常发生吗?
1 in 8.
1/8的可能性
We found the one.
看来你已经看到一个了
You ask amber how the first 2 women died?
你曾问过amber 那两个人是怎么死的了吗?
She's done it before,tony.
她以前就做过这事 tony
No,she hasn'T.
没有 不是她做的
Yes,she has,with other men.
她确实做过 和别的人一起做的
You're not so special.
你不是她的唯一
Men mean nothing to her.
男人对她来说根本不算什么
She used you,just like the other guy.
她在利用你 就象利用其他人一样
Shut up.
闭嘴
She set you up,tony.
她在陷害你tony
She had you do everything.
她让你出去打头阵送死
Whose dna do you think that was at the scene?
知道现场有谁的DNA吗?
Come on.Think about it.
想想吧
Amber beat herself up,she walked in here,she handed me laura clemensen's ring,
amber打伤了她自己 然后过来 给了我laura clemensen的戒指
and she told us you gave it to her as a gift.
告诉我们那个戒指是你送给她的
You know it's true,and that's why you're upset.
你知道我说的都是实话 所以你才会这么的难过
Gideon,garcia found out that amber was abused by her brother and her father.
Gideon garcia发现amber曾受她父兄的虐待
They'd take her to the woods.
他们曾把amber扔在树林里
She betrayed you,tony.
她背叛了你 tony
There's only one way to get her back.
跟我们合作才能把她找回来
Because if you don't,she'll forget about you,just like this other guy.
要不然 她也会象抛弃其他人那样 很快把你也给抛弃的
Tell us where she's keeping the girl.
所以告诉我们那个女孩关在哪里
I know amber's father kept her in the woods so no one would hear her scream.
据我所知 amber的爸爸曾把她扔在树林里 那样就没有人可以听的见她的叫喊了
Was it amber's idea to leave the girls in the woods?
是amber要把那些女孩扔在林子里的吗?
Where's tiffany?
tiffany在哪?
There's a cabin.
有一间小屋
duval county woods
杜瓦尔郡森林
Go!
行动!
Fbi!
FBI!
Back off!
后退!
Amber: You got nothin' on me.
你们不能拿我怎么样的
Yeah,we just got your voice on the tapes giving the orders.
我们已经在DVD上收集到你的罪证了
So what?
那又如何?
He saved one little whore.
他只是救了一个小婊子
Tiffany,I'm fbi.
Tiffany 我是FBI
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我不会伤害你的
Look at me.
相信我
She'll never be the same.
她不可能再回到原来的生活去了
Morgan: You're ok.
你会没事的
You're ok.
没有事了
We got amber.
我们抓到amber了
Tiffany spears is alive.
Tiffany spears还活着
All right.Thank you.
好的 好的 谢谢
Jacksonville P.D.Found the remains of a body on the grounds of the cabin.
杰克逊维尔警方在小屋外的地上 发现了另外一具尸体
They think it's amber canardo's old boyfriend.
怀疑是amber canardo的前男友
And 10'll get 20 that dna'll match the first 2 victims.
我打赌他的DNA会和 那两个受害者身上的一致
At least the families will finally have closure.
至少那些家庭的灾难都可以结束了
And we did save tiffany spears.
我们救出了tiffany spears
Hotch: Philosopher khalil gibran wrote,"out of suffering have emerged the strongest souls.
哲人哈利勒・纪伯伦曾说过 受苦能凸显坚强的灵魂
The most massive characters are seared with scars.
最明显的特征就是 那伤口痊愈的疤痕